const theme_Questions_Cyclon = [
  [
    { id: 1, title: "The Cyclon program" },
    {
      id: 2,
      idTitle: 1,
      question: "What is Cyclon?",
      answer:
        "As part of On's commitment to sustainability, Cyclon™ is On's circularity program. We produce gear that is 100% recyclable, you wear it out, and then we turn it into something new. Think: Run. Recycle. Repeat.",
    },
    {
      id: 3,
      idTitle: 1,
      question: "What is circularity?",
      answer:
        "Circularity means taking material used to make a product and continuing to give it new life. Instead of throwing the gear away, you recycle it and use it over and over again.",
    },
    {
      id: 4,
      idTitle: 1,
      question: "Why has On started Cyclon?",
      answer:
        "We envision a fossil-free future where every On product is engineered for circularity. Cyclon™ takes us one step closer towards that vision.",
    },
    {
      id: 5,
      idTitle: 1,
      question: "What are the Cyclon products?",
      answer:
        "The Cyclon™ program currently includes two circular products: the Cloudneo and Cyclon-T.",
    },
    {
      id: 6,
      idTitle: 1,
      question: "Where is the Cyclon available?",
      answer:
        "Cyclon™ is currently available in 33 countries: Andorra, Austria, Belgium, Bulgaria, Canada, China, Cyprus, Czech Republic, Denmark, Estonia, Finland, France, Germany, Greece, Hungary, Italy, Ireland, Japan, Latvia, Lithuania, Luxembourg, Malta, Monaco, Netherlands, Poland, Portugal, Romania, Slovakia, Slovenia, Spain, Sweden, Switzerland, the United Kingdom and United States.",
    },
    {
      id: 7,
      idTitle: 1,
      question: "Why is cyclon not available world wild?",
      answer:
        "Cyclon™ is live in areas where we have high consumer interest. This allows us to establish circular practices and build systems that are efficient (you know, zero-waste vision and all.)",
    },
  ],
  [
    { id: 8, title: "Cloudneo" },
    {
      id: 9,
      idTitle: 8,
      question: "What is Cloud neo?",
      answer:
        "The Cloudneo is the high-performance running shoe you will never own. Bio-based and 100% recyclable, it's the first shoe in our Cyclon™ circularity program. Most importantly: It's only available via subscription.",
    },

    {
      id: 10,
      idTitle: 8,
      question: "How can I get Cloudneo?",
      answer:
        "You subscribe to it and run in it until you can't anymore. Subscribers can replace the Cloudneo as frequently as every 90 days. However, we anticipate most customers will need a replacement every 6 months. When you're done, request a new Cloudneo, and recycle the old one. Is the Cloudneo right for you? Check it out here.",
    },
    {
      id: 11,
      idTitle: 8,
      question: "What if i lost my pre paid label?",
      answer:
        "Please reach out to us through our Contact Us form. We're happy to help you with this.",
    },
    {
      id: 12,
      idTitle: 8,
      question: "Is the Cloudneo sustainable running?",
      answer:
        "The revolutionary castor bean material is not only recyclable but also ultralight. The upper is minimal, breathable and pretty much unstoppable. For the sole, we used a groundbreaking new engineering process to create a unique foam that returns energy like our teammate Roger (yes, that Roger) returns second serves. Cloud elements cushion your landing before firing you into a seriously powerful push-off. If you were looking for proof that sustainability doesn't mean less performance ability, well, look no further.",
    },
    {
      id: 13,
      idTitle: 8,
      question: "what is the shoes made of?",
      answer:
        "The Cloudneo is engineered from two types of high-quality, high-performance polyamides. The upper is engineered from PA11, a bio-based polyamide derived from castor beans. The bottom unit is engineered from an equally high-performance polyamide compound called Pebax. Not only is the Cloudneo majority bio-based, it’s 100% recyclable and exceptionally high performance.",
    },
    {
      id: 14,
      idTitle: 8,
      question: "where is the Cloudneo manufactured?",
      answer:
        "The Cloudneo is manufactured in Vietnam, like many of our other shoes. When you're on a mission to make a seriously amazing shoe, only the best will do. And our Vietnamese friends are serious shoe-engineering pros. You can find more detail about our factories and conditions here.",
    },
  ],
  [
    { id: 15, title: "Cyclon-T" },
    {
      id: 16,
      idTitle: 15,
      question: "What is Cyclon-T?",
      answer:
        "It's part of our Cyclon™ circularity program and comes from the same castor beans as the Cloudneo. This means they can both be recycled to create new gear.",
    },
    {
      id: 17,
      idTitle: 15,
      question: "What is Cyclon-T made of?",
      answer:
        "There is no subscription for the Cyclon-T. Unlike the Cloudneo, you own the Cyclon-T. It is a one-off purchase. But we still recommend recycling for circularity.",
    },
    {
      id: 18,
      idTitle: 15,
      question: "How doea the Cyclon-T get recycled?",
      answer:
        "Once the t-shirt is totally worn out, please send it back to us. It comes from the same material as the Cloudneo, so we can recycle them both together. Run. Recycle. Repeat. It's that easy.",
    },
    {
      id: 19,
      idTitle: 15,
      question: "What can I do if I haven't receive my package?",
      answer:
        "We’re sorry you're still waiting for your order. No one likes waiting longer than they have to for new gear. For updates on where your order is in the process, ask our On Chatbot! You can also get in touch with our Happiness Delivery team through the Contact Us form on our website, and they'll investigate the details of your order's whereabouts. In the meantime, if you have not already, visit our Order Tracker for the latest update on your order.",
    },
  ],
  [
    { id: 20, title: "Subscription" },
    {
      id: 21,
      idTitle: 20,
      question: "Why should I subscribe to On running?",
      answer:
        "With the subscription service, we have opened up a completely new business model in the sports industry. This is a great opportunity to further educate our consumers about a circular economy, but we're just getting started. We have a long road ahead, which is why we aim to learn from our own channels first, before we offer the model through our retail partners.",
    },
    {
      id: 22,
      idTitle: 20,
      question: "How did you determine the price?",
      answer:
        "The price of a 6-month shoe subscription is the same as the industry average price for high performance running footwear. We do target specific audiences across our product offerings and believe our price is right where it needs to be to garner interest.",
    },
    {
      id: 23,
      idTitle: 20,
      question: "Where can I subscribe to the Cloudneo?",
      answer:
        "To subscribe, follow this link: www.on-running.com/cyclon. Hit the “Subscribe” button to get your hands on the future of running. If you're late to the game, the next loop is coming. Keep your eyes on your inbox to get a head start.",
    },
    {
      id: 24,
      idTitle: 20,
      question: "Can I purchase the cloudeneo without subscripition?",
      answer:
        "We call the Cloudneo “The running shoe you'll never own” for a good reason. The Cyclon™ service wouldn’t meet our sustainability goals if we didn't get them back. On our mission to use less virgin material, we need the shoes back to keep recycling them, so Cloudneo is only available through subscription. But if you really want to purchase a high-performance shoe, then you've come to the right place. We have quite a few of those available too …",
    },
  ],
];

export default theme_Questions_Cyclon;
